Yeah, I guess so. Why lol?
Roman is, I quote, and it's really not extra.
It wasn't the opponent, nailed it.
Too much still.
Aha, now you're talking about TKs.
You can't be serious.
At least I do enough, little damage.
Because it's team damage. At least I do enough, little team damage.
Dude, too much still.
That's not an argument.
What was that? I didn't even expect this context.
I expected the context of grandmother.
And it's really not extra.
Aha, like that. It's really not extra.
The only time...
Yes, yes.
It's really not extra. The only time he really stood between the opponent.
There I just saw something moving and panicked.
Yeah, Dash, it wasn't the opponent.
But I remember a Vertigo clip.
And there you are.
Basically standing on the headshot angle.
He was Genny. He was on AFD.
And then he flies.
On you.