What does that mean?
Short dead, yes.
Do we have more?
I don't know.
Holy shit!
No, I don't see one!
There's one more.
I don't know where he is.
So, David, the boost is an option, right?
Oh, you have the boxes behind you?
Yes.
Yes, I have the scaffold,
so that they can see it.
But I don't see him.
Nice.
One is on my right.
Here, one is coming.
No, there's more in the four.
No?
No.
Here, too.
That's just not...
You can't quantify that
with money.
That doesn't work, David.
The M2-49 is
the most powerful and the best.
I just say
troll.
Do you hear what a
intense troll is?
True.
Actually, true.
For example,
a deagle
costs $100 more.
I'm coming with you.
Nice.
No bullet.
You should be tagged, probably immigration.
Nice.
He shoots second today.
Okay.